<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogging on silentFellow Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blogging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogging on silentFellow Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:50:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Set Up My Blogs With Hugo Hugo Project Setup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-i-set-up-my-blogs-with-hugo-hugo-project-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:50:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-i-set-up-my-blogs-with-hugo-hugo-project-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a&#xA;  href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/why-i-started-blogging&#34;&#xA;  target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA;  rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;  this article&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, I discussed the reason behind starting this blog. Here, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through how I set up this website with &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; — a static site generator. In the next parts, I&amp;rsquo;ll also talk about building your own custom theme, integrating &lt;code&gt;tailwind css&lt;/code&gt;, adding search functionality, and showing similar post recommendations in a simple way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-hugo&#34;&gt;Why Hugo&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I started blogging, I wanted a simple, no-shenanigan, text-based blogging site with minimal &lt;code&gt;js&lt;/code&gt; and a good &lt;code&gt;SEO&lt;/code&gt;. While searching I came across &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; — A simple static site generation tool that converts &lt;code&gt;markdown&lt;/code&gt; into &lt;code&gt;html&lt;/code&gt; for blogs. As a developer and the nature of &lt;code&gt;markdown&lt;/code&gt; to be simple, I love &lt;code&gt;markdown&lt;/code&gt; to take down notes. So when &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; offers this flexibility I prefer &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Started Blogging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/why-i-started-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:54:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/why-i-started-blogging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And I quote, Modern society, especially social media, pushes us to believe that in order to improve, we must constantly consume a lot of information(whether it&amp;rsquo;s needed or not). This makes us constantly consume things around us - passively. In this process we forget to take a deep breath, relax, and allow things to happen. This FOMO makes us restless, making us forget the existence of our inner voice, the concept of deep thinking. This thought hit me in the recent times when I realized I was scrolling endlessly without actually absorbing anything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
